It's just friends talking.
Yeah.
Friends.
Talking.
Yeah.
Deal.
Looks like things are going well.
That's a good sign.
Li Haoyu said
Li Haoyu's dad was
very angry about
Gu Chenyang's secret basketball game.
Maybe this time
we made it to the knockout tournament
changed his mind.
I don't think so.
It's hard to change
an adult's mind.
His coming this time
must be for a reason.
That's true.
Could it be
that he's here to assess us?
It's possible.
So, did we pass the assessment?
I don't know.
So, next,
should we perform well
to help Gu Chenyang?
How do you plan to help?
Gu Chenyang's dad values academics the most.
We should work hard
on both basketball and study.
This is what you should do.
And
the monthly quiz is coming next week.
Lin Qingyuan,
study.
You must study.
For Gu Chenyang,
for his dad,
for the club to be recognized,
and for yourself.
Let's go.
Okay.
Your reaction speed is good.
No wonder Gu Chenyang
asked you to train Chen Song.
Of course.
Hello, Ms. Zhong.
Heaping up earth makes a mountain;
rain and wind arise therefrom.
When water accumulates,
dragons live there.
When kindness accumulates,
one becomes virtuous,
and wise.
Therefore,
one cannot travel far
without taking small steps.
One cannot form a river
without small streams.
Good.
You've been working hard on training,
and you haven't neglected your studies.
Keep it up.
Thank you, sir.
Goodbye, sir.
Nice.
Go.
Look at these three auxiliary lines.
The key here
is to find the hidden
the hidden equal relationship,
which is to construct an auxiliary function.
That's right.
Now that you've got the idea,
it's just a matter of calculation.
Got it.
Thank you, sir.
You've made great progress recently.
Is it because the knockout tournament
is coming up soon?
you've become more motivated in your studies.
Sir,
how do you know?
I often hear the students talk about it.
They say you play very well.
Really?
We're that popular now?
Did they say anything else?
Did anyone compliment me specifically?
Don't get too proud.
Only humility leads to progress.
Modest as I am,
I must be proud
when I'm proud.
Sir, you don't know.
When our Basketball Club
was first formed,
it was so miserable.
No one came to sign up.
I didn't expect that
we can finally
hold our heads high.
Keep working hard.
I'll be on my way now.
Thank you, sir.
Goodbye, sir.
Goodbye.
[The Chinese writing system]
[has evolved since ancient times.]
[Learning Chinese allows us]
[to connect with our ancestors.]
[Written Chinese has also been improved]
[to be used by future generations.]
Good game.
Principal.
You guys
insisted on
starting a basketball club,
saying you could run it yourselves.
Honestly, I didn't believe it.
But I had to give you a chance
to try,
so I said yes.
I never expected
to see you
turn the impossible
into possible, step by step.
Actually, we didn't expect it either.
Now, you must think big.
There's just one more game
before the provincial top eight.
You must defeat your opponents
and achieve good results.
I'm waiting for your good news.
Yes!
Come on.
Good luck.
See you, principal.
See you.
Experimental High School No. 5 is a new team.
It's their first time in the knockout tournament.
There's not much information
about them online.
The only reference we have
is these videos
of these group stage games.
Alright.
I'll do
a preliminary analysis later.
Li Haoyu and his team
are also inquiring about the starting lineup.
I heard two of them
were quite famous in middle school.
As expected,
those who make it to the knockout tournament
are all skilled.
Don't worry.
We're not bad either.
What are you doing?
Filming you guys.
I registered an official account
for our basketball team.
It's the same name across all platforms.
From now on,
there will be not only photos,
but also short videos,
vlogs, and behind-the-scenes footage.
How's that?
Later,
I want to make personal short films
for each of you
to show
another side of you in the team.
As long as you're happy.
You do have a few fans now.
Currently,
they're all friends and family.
No real fans yet.
Real fans?
Here comes a real fan.
Hello.
Xie Yizhou,
I'm Cheng Ke, the coach
of Yudong Basketball Team.
Coach Cheng.
It's you again.
I'm not thinking about
going to Yudong High School.
Please don't...
Don't say no just yet.
Do you know
Gu Chenyang from Yibei Middle School?
Yeah.
What about him?
He might be transferring
to Yudong.
If you change your mind,
give me a call.
Hello, come in.
Why are you so late?
Dad.
Yangyang.
This is...
You know him, right?
Coach Cheng.
Hello, Gu Chenyang.
What are you waiting for?
Come on.
Hello.
Coach Cheng, here's the thing.
I
didn't tell my son.
I wanted to surprise him.
I heard
you're interested in joining Yudong.
So I thought we could talk today
and get to know each other.
Yeah.
I...
Let's get to know each other.
and have a good talk with the coach.
Come on.
Have a seat.
Sit, sit.
Wait a moment.
You sit here,
next to the coach.
Have a good chat.
Give me the bag.
Coach Cheng,
I must toast you again with this one.
I know Yudong
is full of talent.
If my son is fortunate enough
to get in,
I'll need your help.
Thank you.
No problem.
We'll definitely
pay attention to a good seed.
Dad,
don't drink too much.
Drink less?
Let me tell you,
Coach Cheng
is hard to meet.
It took me three tries to get an appointment.
Three times, right?
Yes.
Finally got him out,
I must drink to my heart's content.
Coach Cheng,
Yudong Middle School
is indeed an excellent team.
But actually...
Actually,
Yudong has always
selected players from the middle schools
of various universities.
Because we have our own
training system.
It's rare for someone like you,
transferring in during your first year of high school,
to have a precedent.
But actually...
But
your father went through many channels
to find the principal
and then got in touch with me.
It's mainly because of you
who has a keen eye for talent,
knowing that the child
is still somewhat teachable,
right?
Come on.
Professor Gu has put in
a lot of effort for you.
Gu Chenyang,
I've seen you play.
You're outstanding.
If you weren't so good,
no matter how strong the connections,
we wouldn't have let you in.
Exactly.
Cheers.
By the way,
what were you trying to say earlier?
Go ahead,
if you have anything to say,
just tell Coach Cheng.
Nothing, Coach Cheng.
It's fine.
Let's eat.
He's just shy.
Too shy.
You...
Take the orange juice
and propose a toast to Mr. Cheng.
Show your sincerity.
This kid.
Mr. Cheng, thank you.
Keep it up.
Dad, try this.
You too.
Eat something.
Slow down.
It's okay.
Coach Cheng,
don't drink too much.
Dad hasn't drunk like this in a long time.
He's feeling awful.
What's wrong, Yang?
You've been
so quiet and
unhappy all the way back.
Tell me what's going on.
Dad,
you didn't keep your word.
I didn't keep my word?
What do you mean?
Be more specific.
You said you'd support me.
I did support you.
I did.
You saw how drunk
I was earlier.
I worked so hard,
spent so much time,
and used so many connections
to help you switch teams.
All for you!
But I want to stay at Yibei to play.
Why stay at Yibei?
They don't even have a proper court,
just one public court.
No proper coach,
just an intern.
What kind of strategy can he come up with?
You'll have to help with that.
And they call it having
a data analyst,
but it's just a high school student.
Isn't this just a makeshift team?
How far can they go?
Whether we can go far
we won't know until we try.
Try?
With what?
Tell me, with what?
With your future?
Listen,
it's not happening.
I'm your father,
and I won't allow it.
Dad,
I know why you won't leave.
I know why you
insist on staying in Yibei.
It's because of your friends, isn't it?
Your friendship,
right?
Let me tell you,
compared to your own future,
your prospects,
that friendship is nothing.
Dad,
You never...
Enough.
It's settled.
I won't explain anymore.
You may not understand now,
but one day,
you will.
And you'll thank me.
What's so great about Yibei?
It's just a makeshift team.
How far can it go?
You should understand him.
He's put in a lot of effort
to get you into Yudong.
Even if you don't want to go,
just do him a favor
and check it out.
Mom,
do you think I should transfer?
Objectively speaking,
Yudong is a better platform.
As parents,
we want to do our best
to help you
reach higher places.
But
I can understand you.
You don't want to leave your friends,
or
the grades
you've worked so hard for.
Life is all about
making constant trade-offs.
Son,
the troubles you're facing now
are a part of growing up.
But
is there a right answer
to this kind of growth?
Of course not.
So,
no matter how you choose,
I'm here for you.
Mom,
thank you.
Get some rest.
Okay.
You're really going all out
for our official account.
Of course.
Now that I'm not on the court,
I want to be like Fu Binyan,
shining in my own way,
in my own position.
Our basketball team
is becoming more and more comprehensive.
Gu Chenyang,
how are you going to shoot this time?
For individual member display,
I'll let him play tennis,
play the piano, or something like that.
What about yours?
Have you thought it through?
No.
I don't have
any special skills.
I'll think about it.
Okay.
It's weird.
Gu Chenyang hasn't
responded to my messages
since last night.
I'm almost at his doorstep.
Should I call him?
We can't be late today.
This is the car?
Xu Anbo.
Sorry,
I have something come up.
I can't do the shoot today.
Where are you going?
We're already
at your door.
Are you heading to Yudong Middle School?
Yes, Yudong Middle School.
Yang, get in the car.
Hello?
Xu Anbo.
Yang, get in the car and tell me.
We're running out of time.
Hurry up.
What's going on?
Isn't he at home?
Oh no.
Go!
What's going on?
Gu Chenyang
is going to Yudong Middle School.
What?
Sit in the back.
Okay.
Sir,
Yudong Middle School.
Professor Gu.
Coach Cheng.
Welcome.
Gu Chenyang,
welcome.
Let's go inside and have a look.
Let's go.
Come on, Yangyang.
What are you waiting for?
Look,
he's right there.
It really is Gu Chenyang.
What's he doing in Yudong?
Let's go check it out.
Coach Cheng,
thank you for taking the time
to show us around.
This basketball center
in Yudong
is truly impressive.
You're welcome.
Professor Gu,
we still have
another round of interviews,
It's just a formality.
As long as Gu Chenyang is willing,
we welcome him at any time.
Thank you, thank you.
By the way,
Gu Chenyang,
I just found out
that our team members
had a fight with them.
Guo Rui and his teammates are from the second team.
They're currently facing disciplinary actions
and are suspended from training.
Yudong has always been fair in rewards and punishments.
You can rest assured about that.
That's good.
So, you sent out the second team that day?
Yes.
To compete against Yibei,
the second team is enough.
By the way,
This jersey
is a gift for you.
What's going on?
Keep it down.
Say thank you to the coach.
Thank you, Coach Cheng.
You're welcome.
Okay.
You should get back to work.
We'll be on our way.
It's just as we imagined.
Looks great.
Yang, are you satisfied now?
Let me tell you,
Yudong's conditions
are far superior to Yibei's.
We made the right decision
to move here.
Dad,
I need some time alone.
Alright, alright.
He'll make his own decision.
You've been tired all day.
Take a break.
I'll make you a pot of chrysanthemum tea
to cool you down.
This is our training center
that was upgraded
last year.
The hardware standards
are comparable to professional training camps.
Meanwhile,
we have a top-notch coaching staff
and logistics support team
to fully support the players
in achieving the most efficient growth.
Over the past few years,
we have been able to
provide talents to the Chinese Basketball Association
and the youth teams.
There are also guaranteed spots
at key universities.
As long as you excel,
we'll pave the way for you.
We have long-term exchanges
with many overseas high school leagues,
with annual visits and games,
which are very beneficial
for broadening horizons.
Yang,
I'll just say this to you.
Those who ultimately
reach the top of the pyramid
[are often lonely.]
[You can't]
[have both grades]
[and friendship.]
[If they really consider you a friend,]
[I believe]
[they will support you]
[to make the best choice.]
What are you doing?
Get changed and start training.
Don't just stand there!
Gu Chenyang,
where were you on Saturday?
Xu Anbo and I went to meet you,
but you stood us up.
I'm sorry.
I really had something come up that day.
This week,
I'll make it up to you.
What's going on?
Why so urgent?
Just tell me.
You must have a reason for standing me up.
I...
What's going on
between you two?
Say something!
Let go of me!
Lin Qingyuan, what's your problem?
What's my problem?
Gu Chenyang,
You won't tell me, huh?
What's going on?
Where are you two going?
I'll go check.
You go too.
Change clothes for training.